Finding Aid for the Yvar Mikhashoff Trust for New Music Records, 1996-2011
State University of New York at Buffalo, Music Library
- 2008, XII.; Item 2008-001-2008-260
  - Applications (Pianist and Composer), 2008, B.; Item 2008-004-2008-049
    - Gonzales, Blas, Ng, Wah-hei (Box 64, Item 2008-016)
    - Greenberg, Jacob, Wolek, Kryzsztof (Box 64, Item 2008-017)
    - Gu, Sandra, Broberg, Kirsten (Box 65, Item 2008-018)
    - Hanlon, David, Cerrone, Christopher (Box 65, Item 2008-019)
    - Hartman, Maya, Sivan, Noam (Box 65, Item 2008-020)
    - Huebner, Eric, Cavallone, Paolo (Box 65, Item 2008-021)
    - Hribar, Ashley, Williams, Natalie (Box 65, Item 2008-022)
    - Ibanez, Lluisa, Quintana, Josep (Box 65, Item 2008-023)
    - Johnson, Lura, Adashi, Judah (Box 65, Item 2008-024)
    - Jvania, Nino, Chabashvili, Eka (Box 65, Item 2008-025)
    - Kalhous, David, Nagy, Zvonimir (Box 65, Item 2008-026)
    - Kanga, Zubin, Hollington, Barnaby (Box 65, Item 2008-027)
    - Kinsella, Brendan, Zhou, Xu (Box 65, Item 2008-028)
    - Kirchoff, Keith, Moore, Christopher (Box 65, Item 2008-029)
    - Lieurance, Barbara, Jacoby, Derek (Box 65, Item 2008-030)
    - Manor, Yael, Hochman, Gilad (Box 65, Item 2008-031)
    - Manzo, Emily, Latham, Clara (Box 65, Item 2008-032)
    - McCright, Matthew, Liddell, Patrick (Box 66, Item 2008-033)
    - McKiggan, Christopher, Prangcharoen, Narong (Box 66, Item 2008-034)
    - Mineva, Daniela, Brakel, Christopher (Box 66, Item 2008-035)
    - Mitchell, Robert (Bobby), Plylar, David (Box 66, Item 2008-036)
    - Nakamura, Rei, Black, Annesley (Box 66, Item 2008-037)
    - Nguyen, Brendan, McCormack, Timothy (Box 66, Item 2008-038)
    - O'Connell, Isabelle, Holt, James (Box 66, Item 2008-039)
    - Rohlfing, Renate, Stumpff, Nathan J. (Box 66, Item 2008-040)
    - Rosenkranz, Thomas, Yen, Ming-Hsiu (Box 66, Item 2008-041)
    - Russo, Andrew, Haber, Yotam (Box 66, Item 2008-042)
    - Spiegel, Daniel, Francis, Ryan (Box 66, Item 2008-043)
    - Tchekoratova, Lora, Warshaw, Dalit (Box 66, Item 2008-044)
    - Theodorakis, Ermis, Kojs, Juraj (Box 66, Item 2008-045)
    - Tritschler, Marc, Lin, Meng-Chia (Box 66, Item 2008-046)
    - Van Haegenborgh, Heleen, Smetryns, Thomas (Box 66, Item 2008-047)
    - Weng, Lei, da Silva, Patricio (Box 66, Item 2008-048)
    - Wunsch, Aaron, Grossman, Jorge (Box 66, Item 2008-049)
  - Audio and video recordings, 2008, C.; Item 2008-050-2008-206
    Arranged in two alphabetical sequences: pianists then composers.
    - Andres, Timothy (Box 67, Item 2008-050)
    - Andres, Timothy (Box 67, Item 2008-051)
    - Antoniadis, Pavlos (Box 67, Item 2008-052)
    - Antoniadis, Pavlos (Box 67, Item 2008-053)
    - Arnone, Augustus (Box 67, Item 2008-054)
    - Arnone, Augustus (Box 67, Item 2008-055)
    - Arnone, Augustus (Box 67, Item 2008-056)
    - Barelos, Stacey (Box 67, Item 2008-057)
    - Barelos, Stacey (Box 67, Item 2008-058)
    - Barger, Laura (Box 67, Item 2008-059)
    - Barger, Laura (Box 67, Item 2008-060)
    - Bellheim, Markus (Box 67, Item 2008-061)
    - Bellheim, Markus (Box 67, Item 2008-062)
    - Bengston, Matthew (Box 67, Item 2008-063)
    - Bengston, Matthew (Box 67, Item 2008-064)
    - Bob, Sarah (Box 67, Item 2008-065)
    - Bob, Sarah (Box 67, Item 2008-066)
    - Chang, Jihye (Box 67, Item 2008-067)
    - Chang, Jihye (Box 67, Item 2008-068)
    - Chang, Jihye (Box 67, Item 2008-069)
    - Chang, Jihye (Box 67, Item 2008-070)
    - Chang, Jihye (Box 67, Item 2008-071)
    - Cheng, Amy I-Lin (Box 67, Item 2008-072)
    - Cheng, Amy I-Lin (Box 67, Item 2008-073)
    - Croene, Frederik (Box 67, Item 2008-074)
    - Croene, Frederik (Box 67, Item 2008-075)
    - Croene, Frederik (Box 67, Item 2008-076)
    - Ding, Shiau-uen (Box 67, Item 2008-077)
    - Ding, Shiau-uen (Box 67, Item 2008-078)
    - Ding, Shiau-uen (Box 67, Item 2008-079)
    - Dudley, Sonia (Box 67, Item 2008-080)
    - Dudley, Sonia (Box 67, Item 2008-081)
    - Gonzales, Blas (Box 67, Item 2008-082)
    - Gonzales, Blas (Box 67, Item 2008-083)
    - Greenberg, Jacob (Box 67, Item 2008-084)
    - Greenberg, Jacob (Box 67, Item 2008-085)
    - Gu, Sandra (Box 68, Item 2008-086)
    - Gu, Sandra (Box 68, Item 2008-087)
    - Hartman, Maya (Box 68, Item 2008-088)
    - Hartman, Maya (Box 68, Item 2008-089)
    - Hanlon, David (Box 68, Item 2008-090)
    - Hanlon, David (Box 68, Item 2008-091)
    - Hanlon, David (Box 68, Item 2008-092)
    - Hochman, Gilad (Box 68, Item 2008-093)
    - Hribar, Ashley (Box 68, Item 2008-094)
    - Hribar, Ashley (Box 68, Item 2008-095)
    - Huebner, Eric (Box 68, Item 2008-096)
    - Huebner, Eric (Box 68, Item 2008-097)
    - Ibanez, Lluisa (Box 68, Item 2008-098)
    - Ibanez, Lluisa (Box 68, Item 2008-099)
    - Johnson, Lura (Box 68, Item 2008-100)
    - Johnson, Lura (Box 68, Item 2008-101)
    - Jvania, Nino (Box 68, Item 2008-102)
    - Jvania, Nino (Box 68, Item 2008-103)
    - Kalhous, David (Box 68, Item 2008-104)
    - Kalhous, David (Box 68, Item 2008-105)
    - Kanga, Zubin (Box 68, Item 2008-106)
    - Kanga, Zubin (Box 68, Item 2008-107)
    - Kinsella, Brendan (Box 68, Item 2008-108)
    - Kinsella, Brendan (Box 68, Item 2008-109)
    - Kirchoff, Keith (Box 68, Item 2008-110)
    - Kirchoff, Keith (Box 68, Item 2008-111)
    - Kirchoff, Keith (Box 68, Item 2008-112)
    - Kirchoff, Keith (Box 68, Item 2008-113)
    - Lieurance, Barbara (Box 68, Item 2008-114)
    - Lieurance, Barbara (Box 68, Item 2008-115)
    - Lin, Jenny (Box 68, Item 2008-116)
    - Lin, Jenny (Box 68, Item 2008-117)
    - Manor, Yael (Box 68, Item 2008-118)
    - Manzo, Emily (Box 68, Item 2008-119)
    - Manzo, Emily (Box 68, Item 2008-120)
    - Mineva, Daniela (Box 68, Item 2008-121)
    - Mineva, Daniela (Box 68, Item 2008-122)
    - McCright, Matthew (Box 69, Item 2008-123)
    - McCright, Matthew (Box 69, Item 2008-124)
    - McKiggan, Christopher (Box 69, Item 2008-125)
    - McKiggan, Christopher (Box 69, Item 2008-126)
    - Mitchell, Robert (Bobby) (Box 69, Item 2008-127)
    - Mitchell, Robert (Bobby) (Box 69, Item 2008-128)
    - Nakamura, Rei (Box 69, Item 2008-129)
    - Nakamura, Rei (Box 69, Item 2008-130)
    - Nakamura, Rei (Box 69, Item 2008-131)
    - Nakamura, Rei (Box 69, Item 2008-132)
    - Nguyen, Brendan (Box 69, Item 2008-133)
    - Nguyen, Brendan (Box 69, Item 2008-134)
    - O'Connell, Isabelle (Box 69, Item 2008-135)
    - O'Connell, Isabelle (Box 69, Item 2008-136)
    - O'Donnell, Heather (Box 69, Item 2008-137)
    - O'Donnell, Heather (Box 69, Item 2008-138)
    - Rohlfing, Renate (Box 69, Item 2008-139)
    - Rohlfing, Renate (Box 69, Item 2008-140)
    - Rosenkranz, Thomas (Box 69, Item 2008-141)
    - Rosenkranz, Thomas (Box 69, Item 2008-142)
    - Rosenkranz, Thomas (Box 69, Item 2008-143)
    - Russo, Andrew (Box 69, Item 2008-144)
    - Russo, Andrew (Box 69, Item 2008-145)
    - Spiegel, Daniel (Box 69, Item 2008-146)
    - Spiegel, Daniel (Box 69, Item 2008-147)
    - Tchekoratova, Lora (Box 69, Item 2008-148)
    - Tchekoratova, Lora (Box 69, Item 2008-149)
    - Theodorakis, Ermis (Box 69, Item 2008-150)
    - Theodorakis, Ermis (Box 69, Item 2008-151)
    - Tritschler, Marc (Box 69, Item 2008-152)
    - Van Haegenborgh, Heleen (Box 69, Item 2008-153)
    - Van Haegenborgh, Heleen (Box 69, Item 2008-154)
    - Weng, Lei (Box 69, Item 2008-155)
    - Weng, Lei (Box 69, Item 2008-156)
    - Wunsch, Aaron (Box 69, Item 2008-157)
    - Adashi, Judah (Box 69, Item 2008-158)
    - Berkowitz, Aaron (Box 69, Item 2008-159)
    - Black, Annesley (Box 69, Item 2008-160)
    - Brakel, Christopher (Box 69, Item 2008-161)
    - Broberg, Kirsten (Box 69, Item 2008-162)
    - Cavallone, Paolo (Box 69, Item 2008-163)
    - Cerrone, Christopher (Box 69, Item 2008-164)
    - Chabashvili, Eka (Box 69, Item 2008-165)
    - da Silva, Patricio (Box 69, Item 2008-166)
    - Francis, Ryan (Box 69, Item 2008-167)
    - Freeman, Jason (Box 69, Item 2008-168)
    - Freeman, Jason (Box 69, Item 2008-169)
    - Grossman, Jorge (Box 70, Item 2008-170)
    - Haber, Yotam (Box 70, Item 2008-171)
    - Holland, Jonathan (Box 70, Item 2008-172)
    - Hollington, Barnaby (Box 70, Item 2008-173)
    - Holt, James (Box 70, Item 2008-174)
    - Huang, Tsai-Yun (Box 70, Item 2008-175)
    - Imai, Shintaro (Box 70, Item 2008-176)
    - Jacoby, Derek (Box 70, Item 2008-177)
    - Johnson, Derek (Box 70, Item 2008-178)
    - King, Mary (Box 70, Item 2008-179)
    - Klingbeil, Michael (Box 70, Item 2008-180)
    - Kojs, Juraj (Box 70, Item 2008-181)
    - Latham, Clara (Box 70, Item 2008-182)
    - Lee, Damon (Box 70, Item 2008-183)
    - Liddell, Patric (Box 70, Item 2008-184)
    - Maloy, Kristopher (Box 70, Item 2008-185)
    - McCormack, Timothy (Box 70, Item 2008-186)
    - Minikakis, Stratis (Box 70, Item 2008-187)
    - Moore, Christopher (Box 70, Item 2008-188)
    - Muhly, Nico (Box 70, Item 2008-189)
    - Nagy, Zvonimir (Box 70, Item 2008-190)
    - Ng, Wah-hei (Box 70, Item 2008-191)
    - Plylar, David (Box 70, Item 2008-192)
    - Prangcharoen, Narong (Box 70, Item 2008-193)
    - Prins, Stefan (Box 70, Item 2008-194)
    - Quintana, Josep (Box 70, Item 2008-195)
    - Schuessler, Philip (Box 70, Item 2008-196)
    - Sivan, Noam (Box 70, Item 2008-197)
    - Smetryns, Thomas (Box 70, Item 2008-198)
    - Stumpff, Nathan J. (Box 70, Item 2008-199)
    - Verlingieri, Gianluca (Box 70, Item 2008-200)
    - Warshaw, Dalit (Box 70, Item 2008-201)
    - Williams, Natalie (Box 70, Item 2008-202)
    - Wolek, Krzysztof (Box 70, Item 2008-203)
    - Yen, Ming-Hsiu (Box 70, Item 2008-204)
    - Zhou, Xu (Box 70, Item 2008-205)
    - Zhou, Xu (Box 70, Item 2008-206)
  - Scores, 2008, D.; Item 2008-207-2008-261
    Arranged alphabetically by the composer's last name.
    - Adashi, Judah E., 1975- Dark Hours, 2007, 1 score (50 p.); 28 cm. (Box 80, Item 2008-207)
      For bassoon and piano.
    - Berkowitz, Aaron Tony said he saw birds flying, 2003, 5 p. of music; 28 x 43 cm. (Box 80, Item 2008-208)
      For solo piano
    - Black, Annesley, 1979- LAUF (for nine musicians), 2005, 1 score (69 p.); 30 cm. (Box 80, Item 2008-209)
      For flute, oboe, clarinet, piano, violin, viola, violoncello, contrabass, and percussion.
    - Brakel, Christopher D., 1977- Meta-Tango (Solo Piano), 2001, 5 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 80, Item 2008-210)
      For solo piano.
    - Broberg, Kirsten Emergence, 2006, 1 score (11 p.); 28 x 43 cm. (Box 80, Item 2008-211)
      For piano(1) and bowed piano(3).
    - Cavallone, Paolo, 1975- Confini, 2006, 37 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 80, Item 2008-212)
      For piano.
    - Cerrone, Christopher Averno: a fragment, 2005, 1 score and 4 parts (15, [4] p.); 28 x 43 cm. (Box 80, Item 2008-213)
      For soprano, mezzo-soprano, flute, clarinet, percussion, piano, viola, violoncello, and double bass.
    - Chabashvili, Eka Seven Wonders of World (7 novellas for Chamber Composition): The Colossus of Rhodes, 2000, 1 score (11 p.); 30 cm. (Box 80, Item 2008-214)
      For two pianos and darabuka.
    - Da Silva, Patrício Three Movements for Solo Piano, 2007, 31 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 80, Item 2008-215)
    - Francis, Ryan, 1981- Consolations, 2004, 10 p. of music; 29 x 44 cm. (Box 80, Item 2008-216)
    - Freeman, Jason, 1977- Piano etudes, undated, 7 p. of music; 23 x 29 cm. (Box 80, Item 2008-217)
    - Freeman, Jason, 1977- Sonata, undated, 41 p. of music; 29 cm. (Box 80, Item 2008-218)
    - Grossman, Jorge Villavicencio, 1973- Sialia, 2006, 1 score (18 p.); 36 cm. (Box 80, Item 2008-219)
      For clarinet, violoncello, and piano.
    - Haber, Yotam Three Piano Pieces: etude 3, slip, etude 5, 2007, 4, 2, 6 p. of music; 31 cm. (Box 80, Item 2008-220)
    - Hochman, Gilad Slightly Disturbed (monodrama for violin, clarinet and cello), 2006, 1 score (17 p.); 28 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-221)
    - Holland, Jonathan Bailey, 1974- Songs of Experience, 2004, 1 score (24 p.); 28 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-222)
    - Hollington, Barnaby Mechanical Avunculogratulation (ou L'Art de Fabriquer des Machines a Saluer les Oncles), undated, 1 score (80 p.); 30 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-223)
      For solo piano and thirteen other instruments.
    - Holt, James, 1975- Pieces for piano, 2005, 7 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-224)
    - Huang, Tsai-Yun, 1979- Blazing dawn, 2006, 17 p. of music; 36 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-225)
    - Huang, Tsai-Yun, 1979- Full and Empty, undated, 1 score (17 p.); 22 x 28 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-226)
      For string quartet.
    - Huang, Tsai-Yun, 1979- Imaginary Place, 2007, 1 score (10 p.); 44 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-227)
      For piano and 2-channel tape.
    - Imai, Shintaro, 1974- Figure in Movement II, undated, 1 score (11 p.); 30 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-228)
      For piano and real-time audio/visual processing technique.
    - Jacoby, Derek, 1978- In Memoriam: EV1, 2007, 9 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-229)
    - Johnson, Derek, 1978- Balance, 2001, 1 score (41 p.); 28 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-230)
      For violin, viola, cello, and piano.
    - King, Mary Shadow Builders, 2005, 10 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-231)
    - Klingbeil, Michael Monoliths and Interludes, 2002, 33 p. of music; 36 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-232)
    - Kojs, Juraj All Forgotten, 2006, 1 score (18, 5 p.); 22 x 28 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-233)
      For piano and electronics.
    - Latham, Clara Luftkussen, 2003, 9 p. of music; 28 x 44 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-234)
    - Lee, Damon Faim (pour Piano et Sopran), 2004, 1 score (20 p.); 30 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-235)
    - Liddell, Patrick Jessica's Theme Song, 2007, 1 score ([12] p.); 22 x 28 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-236)
      For flute, oboe, clarinet, viola, cello, glockenspiel, piano, and rhythm.
    - Maloy, Kristopher Quartet in Four Actions: I. Rush, 2007, 1 score (16 p.); 28 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-237)
      For clarinet, violin, violoncello, and piano.
    - McCormack, Timothy, 1984- ]regate[ s.p. ]Aggre[, 2007, 1 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-238)
    - Minikakis, Stratis Distillations of the Night, 2006, 1 score (31 p.); 28 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-239)
      For clarinet, violin, viola, cello, and piano.
    - Moore, Christopher Tentacles and Knot Formations, 2007, 1 score (46 p.); 43 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-240)
      For flute/alto flute, clarinet/bass clarinet, bassoon, piano, 2 violins, viola, cello, contrabass.
    - Muhly, Nico Hudson Cycle, 2005, 3 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-241)
    - Nagy, Zvonimir ... of the lake, 2007, 4 p. of music; 29 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-242)
    - Plylar, David Artist's Studio, 2005, 1 score (97 p.); 44 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-243)
    - Prangcharoen, Narong Three Minds, 2003, 24 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-244)
    - Prins, Stefan, 1979- Memory Space #2, 2007, 1 ms. score (viii, 32 p.); 21 x 30 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-245)
      For solo recorder, electric guitar, piano, percussion, double bass, and live electronics.
    - Quintana, Josep l/b, 2006-2007, 1 score (42 p.); 30 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-246)
      For bass clarinet, drums, and piano.
    - Schuessler, Philip T. Roadside Picnic, 2002, 1 score (22 p.); 22 x 28 cm. (Box 81, Item 2008-247)
      For two pianos.
    - Sivan, Noam, 1978- Five Miniatures for Clarinet in B flat and Piano, 2006, 1 score (16 p.); 28 cm. (Box 82, Item 2008-248)
    - Sivan, Noam, 1978- Three Preludes, 2007, 15 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 82, Item 2008-249)
    - Smetryns, Thomas, 1977- About Morse and Mutual Understanding, 2005, 1 ms. score (9 p.); 21 x 30 cm. (Box 82, Item 2008-250)
      For piano (with optional assistant).
    - Stumpff, Nathan J., 1978- Road Trip Songs, Vol. 1, No. 3: Volkswagen Hobo, 2006, 1 score (25 p.); 28 cm. (Box 82, Item 2008-251)
      For male voice and sextet.
    - Verlingieri, Gianluca, 1976- labirinti della memoria, 2007, 13 p. of music; 30 cm. (Box 82, Item 2008-252)
    - Verlingieri, Gianluca, 1976- ricercare su ave maris stella, 2007, 1 score (7 p.); 30 cm. (Box 82, Item 2008-253)
    - Verlingieri, Gianluca, 1976- schubert-fragmente: eleven microludes for piano, violin and cello, 2006, 1 score (23 p.); 30 cm. (Box 82, Item 2008-254)
    - Wah-Hei, Ng, 1982- 3 bagatelles for piano, 2007, 19 p. of music; 31 cm. (Box 82, Item 2008-255)
    - Warshaw, Dalit Hadass, 1974- Dance of the Red Dreidl: theme and variations on a Hebrew Chanukah tune for solo piano, 2007, 32 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 82, Item 2008-256)
    - Williams, Natalie, 1977- Entropy, 2002, 16 p. of music; 30 cm. (Box 82, Item 2008-257)
    - Wolek, Krzysztof For Madmen only!, [2002], 1 score (21 p.); 29 cm. (Box 82, Item 2008-258)
      For tenor saxophone and piano.
    - Yen, Ming-Hsiu Two Old Postcards from Formosa, 2007, 23 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 82, Item 2008-259)
    - Zhou, Xu A Montage Lullaby ----- for piano, 2007, 18 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 82, Item 2008-260)
    - Zhou, Xu Fluctuation, 2006, 1 score (21 p.); 28 cm. (Box 82, Item 2008-261)
      For soprano, flute, clarinet, violin, violoncello, piano, and percussion.
- 2009, XIII.; Item 2009-001-2009-120
  - Award recipients, 2009, A.; Item 2009-001
    - Holt, Danny, Bettison, Oscar (Box 71, Item 2009-001)
  - Applications (Pianist and Composer), 2009, B.; Item 2009-002-2009-023
    - Alexander, David, Stout, Alastair (Box 71, Item 2009-002)
    - Bob, Sarah, Balter, Marcos (Box 71, Item 2009-003)
    - Cambry, Jonathan, Miler, Pierre (Box 71, Item 2009-004)
    - Campbell, Kate, Ippolito, Michael (Box 71, Item 2009-005)
    - Chadwick, Roderick, Gorton, David (Box 71, Item 2009-006)
    - Chai, Jenny, Wang, Jie (Box 71, Item 2009-007)
    - Chen, Phyllis, Yun, Du (Box 71, Item 2009-008)
    - Cheng, Amy I-Lin, Maloy, Kris (Box 71, Item 2009-009)
    - D'Errico, Anna, Roberto, Rusconi (Box 71, Item 2009-010)
    - Ding, Shiau-uen, Schedel, Margaret (Box 71, Item 2009-011)
    - Glazkov, Alexey, Krashenko, Olga (Box 71, Item 2009-012)
    - Hardink, Jason, Osborne, Thomas (Box 71, Item 2009-013)
    - Hsu, Hsing-ay, Kellogg, Daniel (Box 71, Item 2009-014)
    - Kirchoff, Keith, VanHassel, Dan (Box 71, Item 2009-15)
    - Lavandera, Horacio, Mason, Christian (Box 71, Item 2009-016)
    - Lin, Tiffany, Watkins, Zachary (Box 71, Item 2009-017)
    - Manor, Yael, Hochman, Gilad (Box 71, Item 2009-018)
    - McCright, Matthew, Russell, Jonathan (Box 71, Item 2009-019)
    - O'Connell, Isabelle, Power, Karen (Box 71, Item 2009-020)
    - Pestova, Xenia, Di Castri, Zosha (Box 71, Item 2009-021)
    - Shinners, Evan, Roberts, Derek (Box 71, Item 2009-022)
    - Thomas, Spyros, Tzortzis, Nicolas (Box 71, Item 2009-023)
  - Audio and video recordings, 2009, C.; Item 2009-024-2009-093
    - Alexander, David (Box 72, Item 2009-024)
    - Alexander, David (Box 72, Item 2009-025)
    - Bob, Sarah (Box 72, Item 2009-026)
    - Bob, Sarah (Box 72, Item 2009-027)
    - Campbell, Kate (Box 72, Item 2009-028)
    - Campbell, Kate (Box 72, Item 2009-029)
    - Chadwick, Roderick (Box 72, Item 2009-030)
    - Chadwick, Roderick (Box 72, Item 2009-031)
    - Chai, Jenny (Box 72, Item 2009-032)
    - Chai, Jenny (Box 72, Item 2009-033)
    - Chen, Phyllis (Box 72, Item 2009-034)
    - Chen, Phyllis (Box 72, Item 2009-035)
    - Cheng, Amy I-Lin (Box 72, Item 2009-036)
    - D'Errico, Anna (Box 72, Item 2009-037)
    - D'Errico, Anna (Box 72, Item 2009-038)
    - Ding, Shiau-uen (Box 72, Item 2009-039)
    - Ding, Shiau-uen (Box 72, Item 2009-040)
    - Ding, Shiau-uen (Box 72, Item 2009-041)
    - Glazkov, Alexey (Box 72, Item 2009-042)
    - Hardink, Jason (Box 72, Item 2009-043)
    - Hardink, Jason (Box 72, Item 2009-044)
    - Hsu, Hsing-ay (Box 72, Item 2009-045)
    - Hsu, Hsing-ay (Box 72, Item 2009-046)
    - Kirchoff, Keith (Box 72, Item 2009-047)
    - Kirchoff, Keith (Box 72, Item 2009-048)
    - Lavandera, Horacio (Box 72, Item 2009-049)
    - Lavandera, Horacio (Box 72, Item 2009-050)
    - Lin, Tiffany (Box 72, Item 2009-051)
    - Lin, Tiffany (Box 72, Item 2009-052)
    - Manor, Yael (Box 72, Item 2009-053)
    - Manor, Yael (Box 72, Item 2009-054)
    - McCright, Matthew (Box 73, Item 2009-055)
    - McCright, Matthew (Box 73, Item 2009-056)
    - O'Connell, Isabelle (Box 73, Item 2009-057)
    - O'Connell, Isabelle (Box 73, Item 2009-058)
    - Pestova, Xenia (Box 73, Item 2009-059)
    - Pestova, Xenia (Box 73, Item 2009-060)
    - Shinners, Evan (Box 73, Item 2009-061)
    - Shinners, Evan (Box 73, Item 2009-062)
    - Thomas, Spyro (Box 73, Item 2009-063)
    - Thomas, Spyro (Box 73, Item 2009-064)
    - Balter, Marcos (Box 73, Item 2009-065)
    - Di Castri, Zosha (Box 73, Item 2009-066)
    - Gorton, David (Box 73, Item 2009-067)
    - Hochman, Gilad (Box 73, Item 2009-068)
    - Ippolito, Michael (Box 73, Item 2009-069)
    - Jie, Wang (Box 73, Item 2009-070)
    - Jie, Wang (Box 73, Item 2009-071)
    - Kellogg, Daniel (Box 73, Item 2009-072)
    - Krashenko, Olga (Box 73, Item 2009-073)
    - Maloy, Kristopher (Box 73, Item 2009-074)
    - Maloy, Kristopher (Box 73, Item 2009-075)
    - Mason, Christian (Box 73, Item 2009-076)
    - Miller, Pierre (Box 73, Item 2009-077)
    - Osborne, Thomas (Box 73, Item 2009-078)
    - Power, Karen (Box 73, Item 2009-079)
    - Roberto, Rusconi (Box 73, Item 2009-080)
    - Roberts, Derek (Box 73, Item 2009-081)
    - Russell, Jonathan (Box 73, Item 2009-082)
    - Schedel, Margaret (Box 73, Item 2009-083)
    - Stout, Alastair (Box 73, Item 2009-084)
    - Tzortis, Nicolas (Box 73, Item 2009-085)
    - VanHassel, Dan (Box 73, Item 2009-086)
    - Watkins, Zachary (Box 73, Item 2009-087)
    - Yun, Du (Box 73, Item 2009-088)
    - Holt, Danny (Box 73, Item 2009-089)
    - Holt, Danny (Box 73, Item 2009-090)
    - Bettison, Oscar, 1975- (Box 73, Item 2009-091)
    - Bettison, Oscar, 1975- (Box 73, Item 2009-092)
    - Bettison, Oscar, 1975- (Box 73, Item 2009-093)
  - Scores, 2009, D.; Item 2009-094-2009-120
    - Balter, Marcos, 1974- RE: (no subject), 2004, 1 score (26 p.); 28 x 43 cm. (Box 82, Item 2009-094)
    - Bettison, Oscar, 1975- Gauze Vespers, 2007, 1 score (33 p.); 31 cm. (Box 82, Item 2009-095)
      For A clarinet, vibraphone, prepared piano, violin, and cello.
    - Bettison, Oscar, 1975- Inventory of Remnants, 2009, 1 score (28 p.); 31 cm. (Box 82, Item 2009-096)
      For piano and percussion (one player).
    - Bettison, Oscar, 1975- O Death, 2006, 1 score (160 p.); 31 cm. (Box 82, Item 2009-097)
      For two tenor saxophones, trombone, percussion, piano, electric guitar, and electronic equipment.
    - Di Castri, Zosha Thinking Eye, 2006, 2 p. of ms. music; 22 x 36 cm. (Box 82, Item 2009-098)
    - Gorton, David, 1978- Ondine, 2003, 6 p. of music; 30 cm. (Box 82, Item 2009-099)
    - Hochman, Gilad Quest (for saxophone and piano), 2008, 1 score ([11] p.); 28 cm. (Box 82, Item 2009-100)
    - Ippolito, Michael Blackbird Variations, 2003-2004, 17 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 82, Item 2009-101)
    - Jie, Wang Game for Two, 2008, 1 score (27 p.); 36 cm. (Box 82, Item 2009-102)
    - Kellogg, Daniel, 1976- Scarlet Thread, 2004, 12 p. of music; 28 x 36 cm. (Box 82, Item 2009-103)
    - Krashenko, Olga From..., undated, 3 p. of music; 30 cm. (Box 82, Item 2009-104)
      For piano solo.
    - Maloy, Kristopher Quartet in Four Actions, 2007, 1 score (16, 27, 19, 29 p.); 28 cm. (Box 83, Item 2009-105)
    - Mason, Christian, 1984- Equinoxes of the Infinite, 2008, 1 score (17 p.) (Box 83, Item 2009-106)
      For two pianos and percussion.
    - Miller, Pierre (pseudonym A. Nicky Scribs) Three Concert Studies, 2008, 40 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 83, Item 2009-107)
    - Osborne, Thomas, 1978- And the Waves Sing Because They are Moving, 2004, 21 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 83, Item 2009-108)
    - Power, Karen like piglets at a market, 2004, 14 p. of music; 30 cm. (Box 83, Item 2009-109)